const quiz0data = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "Sandra is __ nurse.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "a", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "-", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use a/an when we say what somebody's job is."
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "John had __ sandwich for lunch.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "the", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "a", isCorrect: true}
      ],
      help: 'John says "a sandwich" because this is the first time he talks about it.'
   },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "__ birds eat worms.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "-", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "The", isCorrect: false}
      ],
      help: 'When we talk about things in general, we normally use a plural or uncountable noun with no article.'
   },
  //   {
  //     id: 4,
  //     question: "__ useful tool.",
  //     answersList: [
  //       {answer: "an", isCorrect: false},
  //       {answer: "a", isCorrect: true},
  //     ],
  //     help: "We use 'an' before words starting with vowel sounds. 'Useful' starts with consonant sound."
  //  },
  //   {
  //     id: 5,
  //     question: "__ water freezes at 0c.",
  //     answersList: [
  //       {answer: "The", isCorrect: false},
  //       {answer: "-", isCorrect: true}
  //     ],
  //     help: 'When we talk about things in general, we normally use a plural or uncountable noun with no article.'
  //  },
  //   {
  //     id: 6,
  //     question: "I'm going to __ bed.",
  //     answersList: [
  //       {answer: "-", isCorrect: true},
  //       {answer: "the", isCorrect: false},
  //     ],
  //     help: "We don't usually use an article in expressions with bed, work and  home."
  //  },
  //   {
  //     id: 7,
  //     question: "Joe plays __ piano really well.",
  //     answersList: [
  //       {answer: "-", isCorrect: false},
  //       {answer: "the", isCorrect: true}
  //     ],
  //     help: 'We use "the" to talk about musical instruments.'
  //  },
  //   {
  //     id: 8,
  //     question: "I heard it on ___ radio.",
  //     answersList: [
  //       {answer: "-", isCorrect: false},
  //       {answer: "the", isCorrect: true},
  //     ],
  //     help: 'We use "the" to refer to a system or service.'
  //  },
  //   {
  //     id: 9,
  //     question: "I feel sick today. I will stay at ___ home.",
  //     answersList: [
  //       {answer: "-", isCorrect: true},
  //       {answer: "the", isCorrect: false}
  //     ],
  //     help: "We don't usually use an article in expressions with bed, work and  home."
  //  },
  //   {
  //     id: 10,
  //     question: "You should tell ___ police.",
  //     answersList: [
  //       {answer: "the", isCorrect: true},
  //       {answer: "-", isCorrect: false}
  //     ],
  //     help: 'We use "the" to refer to a system or service.'
  //  },
  //   {
  //     id: 11,
  //     question: "__ Pope is visiting Portugal.",
  //     answersList: [
  //       {answer: "-", isCorrect: false},
  //       {answer: "The", isCorrect: true},
  //     ],
  //     help: 'We use "the" because there is only one Pope.'
  //  },
  //   {
  //     id: 12,
  //     question: "Look at __ boy over there.",
  //     answersList: [
  //       {answer: "a", isCorrect: false},
  //       {answer: "the", isCorrect: true}
  //     ],
  //     help: '= the boy I am pointing at.'
  //  },
  ]
export default quiz0data
